https://noreast.ca/privacy-policy

COVID-19 (Novel Coronavirus) / No Delays
Home>Privacy Policy – Noreast.ca
Privacy Policy - Noreast.ca
This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you may provide on the noreast.ca website (“Website” or “Service”)
and any of its related products and services (collectively, “Services”) is collected, protected and used. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of
your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information. This Policy is a legally binding agreement between you (“User”, “you” or “your”) and Noreast
Electronics Co. Ltd. (“Noreast Electronics Co. Ltd.”, “we”, “us” or “our”). By accessing and using the Website and Services, you acknowledge that you have read, understood,
and agree to be bound by the terms of this Agreement. This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not
employ or manage.
Automatic collection of information
When you open the Website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. This data may include information such as your device’s IP address, browser
type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Website and Services, pages of the Website
and Services that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on the Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.
Information collected automatically is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding the usage and traffic of the Website and
Services. This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that would identify any particular user of the system.
Collection of personal information
You can access and use the Website and Services without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could identify you as a specific, identifiable
individual. If, however, you wish to use some of the features on the Website, you may be asked to provide certain Personal Information (for example, your name and e-mail
address). We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, or fill any online forms on the Website. When required, this
information may include the following:
– Personal details such as name, country of residence, etc.
– Contact information such as email address, address, etc.
– Account details such as user name, unique user ID, password, etc.
You can choose not to provide us with your Personal Information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the features on the Website. Users who are uncertain
about what information is mandatory are welcome to contact us.
Use and processing of collected information
In order to make the Website and Services available to you, or to meet a legal obligation, we need to collect and use certain Personal Information. If you do not provide the
information that we request, we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or services. Some of the information we collect is directly from you via the Website
and Services. However, we may also collect Personal Information about you from other sources. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:
– Create and manage user accounts
– Improve products and services
– Send administrative information
– Send marketing and promotional communications
– Respond to inquiries and offer support
– Request user feedback
– Improve user experience
– Post customer testimonials
– Deliver targeted advertising
– Enforce terms and conditions and policies
– Protect from abuse and malicious users
– Respond to legal requests and prevent harm
– Run and operate the Website and Services
Processing your Personal Information depends on how you interact with the Website and Services, where you are located in the world and if one of the following applies: (i) you
have given your consent for one or more specific purposes; this, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to California Consumer
Privacy Act or European data protection law; (ii) provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations
thereof; (iii) processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject; (iv) processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public
interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in us; (v) processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.
Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. In any case, we will be happy to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
Managing information
You are able to delete certain Personal Information we have about you. The Personal Information you can delete may change as the Website and Services change. When you delete
Personal Information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised Personal Information in our records for the duration necessary for the purposes described below. If you
would like to delete your Personal Information or permanently delete your account, you can do so by contacting us.
Disclosure of information
We will disclose any Personal Information we collect, use or receive if required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, and when we
believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your user account, and Personal
Information will likely be among the assets transferred.
Retention of information
We will retain and use your Personal Information for the period necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements unless a longer
retention period is required or permitted by law. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not
in a manner that would identify you personally. Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure,
the right to rectification and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.
Transfer of information
Depending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own. You are entitled to learn about the legal
basis of information transfers to a country outside the European Union or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more
countries, such as the UN, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information. If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the
relevant sections of this Policy or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.
The rights of users
You may exercise certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following: (i) you have the right to withdraw consent
where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information; (ii) you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing
is carried out on a legal basis other than consent; (iii) you have the right to learn if information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of
the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing; (iv) you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or
corrected; (v) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any
purpose other than storing it; (vi) you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us; (vii) you have the right to
receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any
hindrance. This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which
you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.
The right to object to processing
Where Personal Information is processed for the public interest, in the exercise of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued
by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection.
Data protection rights under GDPR
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights and Noreast Electronics Co. Ltd. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you
to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Information. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be
removed from our systems, please contact us. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
– You have the right to request access to your Personal Information that we store and have the ability to access your Personal Information.
– You have the right to request that we correct any Personal Information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request us to complete the Personal Information
you believe is incomplete.
– You have the right to request the erase your Personal Information under certain conditions of this Policy.
– You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Information.
– You have the right to seek restrictions on the processing of your Personal Information. When you restrict the processing of your Personal Information, we may store it but
will not process it further.
– You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
– You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Noreast Electronics Co. Ltd. relied on your consent to process your Personal Information.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Information. For more information, please contact your local data
protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
California privacy rights
In addition to the rights as explained in this Policy, California residents who provide Personal Information (as defined in the statute) to obtain products or services for
personal, family, or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year, information about the Personal Information we shared, if any, with other
businesses for marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of Personal Information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which
we shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in the current year will receive information about the prior year). To obtain
this information please contact us.
How to exercise these rights
Any requests to exercise your rights can be directed to Noreast Electronics Co. Ltd. through the contact details provided in this document. Please note that we may ask you to
verify your identity before responding to such requests. Your request must provide sufficient information that allows us to verify that you are the person you are claiming to
be or that you are the authorized representative of such person. You must include sufficient details to allow us to properly understand the request and respond to it. We
cannot respond to your request or provide you with Personal Information unless we first verify your identity or authority to make such a request and confirm that the Personal
Information relates to you.
Privacy of children
We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, please do not submit any Personal Information through
the Website and Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their children
never to provide Personal Information through the Website and Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 18 has provided
Personal Information to us through the Website and Services, please contact us. You must also be at least 16 years of age to consent to the processing of your Personal
Information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).
Cookies
The Website and Services use “cookies” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies
cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the
cookie to you.
We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to operate the Website and Services. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not
be able to fully experience the features of the Website and Services. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit internetcookies.org
Do Not Track signals
Some browsers incorporate a Do Not Track feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online activity tracked. Tracking is not the same as using
or collecting information in connection with a website. For these purposes, tracking refers to collecting personally identifiable information from consumers who use or visit a
website or online service as they move across different websites over time. How browsers communicate the Do Not Track signal is not yet uniform. As a result, the Website and
Services are not yet set up to interpret or respond to Do Not Track signals communicated by your browser. Even so, as described in more detail throughout this Policy, we limit
our use and collection of your personal information.
Email marketing
We may offer electronic newsletters to which you may voluntarily subscribe at any time. We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential and will not disclose your
email address to any third parties except as allowed in the information use and processing section or for the purposes of utilizing a third party provider to send such emails.
We will maintain the information sent via e-mail in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.
In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mails sent from us will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. You may
choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by contacting us. However, you will continue
to receive essential transactional emails.
Links to other resources
The Website may contain links to other resources that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such
other resources or third parties. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Website and Services and to read the privacy statements of each and every resource that may
collect Personal Information.
Information security
We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable
administrative, technical, and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its
control and custody. However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed. Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information,
you acknowledge that (i) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (ii) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all
information and data exchanged between you and the Website and Services cannot be guaranteed; and (iii) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit
by a third party, despite best efforts.
Data breach
In the event we become aware that the security of the Website and Services has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as
a result of external activity, including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not
limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities. In the event of a data breach, we will make reasonable
efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law.
When we do, we will post a notice on the Website, send you an email.
Changes and amendments
We reserve the right to modify this Policy or its terms relating to the Website and Services from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any material changes to
the way in which we treat Personal Information. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our
discretion, such as through contact information you have provided. Any updated version of this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Policy
unless otherwise specified. Your continued use of the Website and Services after the effective date of the revised Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will
constitute your consent to those changes. However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Information in a manner materially different than what was stated at
the time your Personal Information was collected.
Acceptance of this policy
You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions. By accessing and using the Website and Services you agree to be bound by this Policy.
If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to access or use the Website and Services.
Contacting us
If you would like to contact us to understand more about this Policy or wish to contact us concerning any matter relating to individual rights and your Personal Information,
you may write a letter to 1175 Tupper Street, Hawkesbury, Ontario, Canada, K6A 3T5
Consent* I agree to allow Noreast Electronics to store and process the data provided.*
